<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BinaryDigit</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on BinaryDigit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>redesign</title>
      <link>/posts/redesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/redesign/</guid>
      <description>I probably won&amp;rsquo;t end up using the blog portion of Hugo since I already have a blog, but I call it &amp;ldquo;site updates&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/index-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/index-about/</guid>
      <description>Hi I&amp;rsquo;m &amp;ldquo;B&amp;rdquo;. By day I&amp;rsquo;m a tech director for a digital media company and in my free time I like to game, mix music, take photos, tinker with code and travel when I can.
I&amp;rsquo;m currently in the process of re-discoverying my creativity and seeing where it can take me next in my career. I try to write about what I&amp;rsquo;m up to on Mastodon or my blog.
I&amp;rsquo;m doing a digital overhaul for the next few months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>/Uses</title>
      <link>/uses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/uses/</guid>
      <description>All of the gear and software that I use everyday.
Hardware Computer Software Development Services Analog Fashion </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Now Page</title>
      <link>/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/now/</guid>
      <description>A /now page is a great way to share what’s going on in your life now. I love to be creative in my personal time (code, art, photography), support open source, and love all things technical, so right now everything intersects well.
Doing Rediscovering things that bring me joy, such a photography, music, light coding/making things pretty. I need more beauty in my life so I want to create it. Playing Street Fighter 6 Mortal Kombat 1 Animal Crossing New Horizons Stardew Valley (I swing from cozy to volent depending on my mood 🤣)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
